24 years. Hi, good day.
I'm just real. I'm 24 years old from Philippines,
so UTC plus 8. Uhm,
I have us, uh, I have over two years of experience as an AI
video editor for e-commerce brands like health and wellness brands.
Beauty and personal care, and now I'm expanding my experience
in fashion brands, so I'm applying for this role,
and, uhm,
I can work up to 40 hours a week.
In a week, I can work full time,
and here's how my AI workflows work.
I use chat GPT to generate,
uhm, AI images.
To generate my prompt,
and also cloud. I use cloud to generate my prompt.
So first, I open my client's briefs here.
To follow instructions, SOPs,
and guidelines on how to generate my images,
videos, and products using Google Drive.
So, I'm also using,
uh, Higgs Field AI.
So, in images, I'm using a Nano Banana Pro here.
If I want the ratio up to 960,
69, whatsoever.
Then, after I generate an image here,
I go to videos, and,
I'm using, uh,
Sedans for AIUGC realistic style,
and I use also Kling. Uh,
mostly I use Kling for generating my images and Gemini Omniflash.
And Google, Google, Google, Vue. For,
and also I have experience in Google Work,
Google Flow. Wait.
Google Flow. I have also experience in Google Flow,
but now, I'm most, mostly I'm using Higgs Field.
Cause, I don't have credits in Google Flow.
On Google Flow.
Wait.
So, it's so long for me to log in,
but yeah, I have experience in Google Flow,
using Google Flow. Using Google Vue,
and then a BananaPro. So that's
all for today, thank you,
and I'm looking forward to talk with you soon,
and I'm looking forward to see you.
meet with you, and looking forward to your response.
Thank you.